this is an official invitation to JP
Sears to come on the idea cafe I just
finished watching your five-step
protocol on the social justice had to be
a social justice warrior online and I
would like to share with you idea cafes
five-step protocol that I just made up
while watching your video and comment it
on your video one each participant gets
to share from their heart what they have
to say in the moment step to listen to
others share from their heart step 3
listen together for our commonalities
step 4 own our own emotions and triggers
while honoring that sometimes this is
hard and we will fail 5 create a social
media platform design for connection in
this format if you want to know what an
idea cafe looks like we've only had two
so far and they've been amazing we are
gonna create the platform designed for
this type of conversation where
everybody gets to come and join and have
their voice heard but right now I'm
reaching out to social media influencers
to come and share their influence come
and be part of a conversation it doesn't
cost you any money just a half an hour
of your time five minutes
speaking from your heart 20 minutes of
listing and five minutes of a
conversation I will create an idea cafe
around a question that is meaningful to
you that we will all take turns
crafting most everyone take turns
answering we can change this world
together it involves true real
connection with one another I invite you
JP Sears to please come and be part of
one idea Cafe thank you